infosnap.com 2015-09-14

# InfoSnap privacy policy

[](http://studentprivacypledge.org/)InfoSnap, Inc. (InfoSnap) is committed to protecting your privacy. Except in limited circumstances described in this Privacy Policy, InfoSnap will NOT sell, trade, transmit or assign any unaggregated, Personally Identifiable Information that it collects to third parties outside of InfoSnap, Schools using InfoSnap for admissions, enrollment, registration, and related services (the “InfoSnap Service”), and the End Users of the InfoSnap Service. This Privacy Policy explains the information gathered by InfoSnap, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. By visiting this website and/or continuing to use InfoSnap, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

We are especially sensitive to the need to protect information concerning children. We do not knowingly solicit information from children under the age 13, and we do not contemplate the transmission of data by children to InfoSnap’s services.

**Click a link below for our policy on each topic:**

  * What is Personally Identifiable Information?
  * What information does InfoSnap collect through its public website, and how is this information used?
  * What information is collected via School and End User usage of the InfoSnap Service, and how is this information used?
  * What other information is collected?
  * How does InfoSnap protect the security of information provided?
  * Under what circumstances must InfoSnap disclose information provided?
  * How can I change, update, or delete the information I’ve provided?
  * How will I be notified of changes to this Privacy Policy?
  * Where are the Sites controlled and operated?
  * How can I contact InfoSnap with questions about this Privacy Policy?

### What is Personally Identifiable Information?

“Personally Identifiable Information” is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable person, such as a person’s first and last name in combination with identifying data such as, postal address, telephone number, or e-mail address.

### What information does InfoSnap collect through its public websites and other sources, and how is this information used?

InfoSnap collects certain Personally Identifiable Information through its public websites when you choose to submit such information to us through an online form, email, or other method. You may provide InfoSnap with information in order to request additional information about the Service, to sign up for a demo, to inquire about employment opportunities, for press inquiries, or for other purposes. Additionally, information may be collected through our social media pages such as LinkedIn, Twitter, and Facebook, as well as through HTML-formatted email messages that we send to you that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Sites”), as well as other sources, such as public databases, joint marketing partners, or from other third parties.

The Personally Identifiable Information we collect is used to better serve our prospects and clients, and to improve our services. For example, we may use this information to respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, such as arranging a demo, provide you with important information about the Sites, such as updates or notices, improve and personalize customer service, and/or in aggregate, guide our marketing efforts and business purposes.

### What information is collected via the InfoSnap Service, and how is this information used?

This section applies to users of the InfoSnap Service. If you only use our public sites, this section does not apply to you. When hosting an InfoSnap Service for a school, school district, or other organization (collectively, the “Schools”), InfoSnap collects and subsequently processes Personally Identifiable Information provided by either or both the End Users or the School. When you as an End User provide information within an InfoSnap Service, it becomes immediately accessible to and controlled by the School using the InfoSnap Service.

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we will not otherwise, in any manner, transmit the information you provide via the InfoSnap Service to any third parties, unless we have to disclose it to comply with legal requirements, or in exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of an InfoSnap End User.

### What other information is collected?

We may also collect information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an individual (“Other Information”). This Other Information may include browser and device information, information collected through cookies, pixel tags, and other technologies, demographic information and other information provided by you, and aggregated information.

To ensure that our Sites and the Services functions properly for all users, we use certain information that is collected by most browsers or automatically through your device. Such things may include whether you are using a Macintosh or Windows computer, your device manufacturer and model, and your Internet browser type and version.

Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the computer that you are using. Cookies allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the Sites, pages visited, languages preferences, and other anonymous traffic data. We do not save cookies to your computer unless it is necessary to perform an action requested by you, such as storing a username for future use. Then, we can recognize your computer to assist your use of the Sites and the Service.

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline cookies, or be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer to your computer of a particular cookie (or cookies) from a particular site. You may also wish to refer to <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html>. However, if you do not accept these cookies, you will experience some inconvenience in your use of the Sites and the Service.

Pixel tags (also known as web beacons and clear GIFs) may be used in connection with some services to, among other things, track the actions of users of the Sites (including email recipients), measure the success of our marketing campaigns and compile statistics about usage of the Sites and response rates.

Your “IP Address” is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). An IP Address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user accesses the Sites, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many webpages, applications and other services. We use IP Addresses for purposes such as calculating usage level of the Sites, helping diagnose server problems, and administering the Sites.

Other Information is also provided directly by you. Information such as your preferred means of communication is collected when you voluntarily provide this information. Unless combined with Personally Identifiable Information, this information does not personally identify you or any other user of the Sites.

Finally, aggregated Personally Identifiable Information does not personally identify you or any other use of the services. For example, we may aggregate Personally Identifiable Information to calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular telephone area code.

Please note that we may use and disclose Other Information, that which does not reveal your identity, for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. However, if we are required to treat Other Information as Personally Identifiable Information under applicable law, then we will use the greater protections afforded to Personally Identifiable Information and may only use it for all the purposes for which we use and disclose Personally Identifiable Information.

In some instances, we may combine Other Information and Personally Identifiable Information (such as combining your name with your zip code). If we combine any Other Information with Personally Identifiable Information, we will treat the combined information as Personally Identifiable Information for as long as it is combined and again follow our stricter privacy protections.

### How does InfoSnap protect the security of information provided?

We consider any information provided by you to be confidential, unless it is publicly available or has already been provided to us without any confidentiality restriction. Only those InfoSnap employees and consultants who need it to perform their job responsibilities are authorized to have access to it.

With respect to InfoSnap Services, it is InfoSnap’s corporate policy to require that the Schools to which we transmit your Personally Identifiable Information agree to comply with our Privacy Policy. InfoSnap protects Personally Identifiable Information from unauthorized disclosure and complies with all applicable State and Federal confidentiality laws and regulations including but not limited to the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA).

We protect your information when it is received by and sent from InfoSnap. We use “encryption” for this purpose, which is the primary means for providing confidentiality for information sent over the internet. When you utilize your web browser to access InfoSnap, you do so over a “secure socket layer” (SSL). It automatically encrypts and protects your transaction with InfoSnap at 128 bits, which is the standard for commercial Internet transactions. Cryptographic algorithms are additionally used for encryption when data is at rest on the InfoSnap servers. We do not use unsecured email transmission for Personally Identifiable Information.

While protecting your privacy is of the utmost importance and we use discretion in selecting only trusted third-parties to provide us with services that support the operation of our business, we cannot guarantee nor can we be responsible for third party practices regarding your privacy. We do not endorse any site or service linked from our website or social media pages and cannot protect any information you disclose to other organizations through our social media pages or website.

Maintaining your privacy is a major focus at InfoSnap. As new technologies and methods become available for increasing your privacy protection, we will carefully examine them for applicability to our business. We seek to use reasonable organization, technical and administrative measures to protect Personally Identifiable Information within our organization. Despite our diligent efforts and implementation of reasonable security measures, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us in according with the “Contacting Us” section below.

### Under what circumstances must InfoSnap disclose information provided?

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose Personally Identifiable Information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith basis to believe that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process.

Also, in the case of any change to InfoSnap’s corporate organization, such as a merger or sale, your Personally Identifiable Information will likely be transferred as part of the restructuring of the overall business.

InfoSnap utilizes trusted, third-party service providers for things like website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, and related business operation. Occasionally, these trusted service providers may need access to your Personally Identifiable Information, which we provide only to the extent necessary for them to perform their specific service.

### How can I change, update, or delete the information I’ve provided?

Please note that any information you post or disclose through social media pages, blogs, etc. will become public information and may be available to users of the sites and to the general public. We urge you to be very careful when deciding to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information, or any other information, on the sites.

With respect to our prospects and clients, we give you many choices regarding our use and disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information for marketing purposes. You may opt-out from receiving electronic marketing-related communications from us on a going-forward basis. You may opt-out of receiving these emails by following the directions included in each communication. You may also opt-out from receiving phone and mail communications by writing to us via email or mail, or telling us on the phone that you’d like to be included on our “do not contact” list.

Your request(s) will be addressed as soon as reasonably practicable. Please also note that if you do opt-out of receiving marketing-related emails from us, we may still send you important administrative messages, and you cannot opt-out of receiving administrative messages.

For End Users of InfoSnap Services, all changes, updates or deletions of Personally Identifiable Information must be made through the course of interacting with the Service that InfoSnap hosts for the School, or by contacting the School directly. All inquiries regarding Personally Identifiable Information should be directed to the School.

### How will I be notified of changes to this Privacy Policy?

InfoSnap will notify End Users of InfoSnap Services of material changes to our Privacy Policy. The changes will be made known to the End User before or at the time of implementation in conjunction with accessing the School’s Service. Users will have a choice to accept these new changes. This is true especially for cases where data will be used differently than outlined in the preceding Privacy Policy.

### Where are the Sites controlled and operated?

The Sites are controlled and operated by us from the United States, and are not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country, or territory other than that of the United States.

### How can I contact InfoSnap with questions about this Privacy Policy?

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [PrivacyPolicy@InfoSnap.com](mailto:PrivacyPolicy@InfoSnap.com) or please write to the following address:

InfoSnap, Inc.  
7700 Old Georgetown Road  
Suite 850  
Bethesda, MD 20814

Please note that email communications are not always secure; so please do not include any sensitive information in your emails to us.
